Hello hello friends,
welcome to the YouTube channel of Kaafi today
in this video we will talk
about the insurance sector,
what is the cotton market situation of the insurance sector,
how will the insurance sector perform in the pregnancy powder film and will know
in detail
what will be the good of the insurance sector in the feature, should one take Rafale Talk
for long term investment in the insurance sector
or what from
Before starting the video if you want to
stay updated with any stock related mutual fund related investment related video and want stock latest
videos regularly please subscribe my channel
and click on the bell icon for future
updates let's watch the video You all must be
knowing that in the event situation due to
coronavirus everything
is flying in the review situation no
work is being done but
what is the good of one's life, every person is able to think in the situation
but even some time ago the
situation of life insurance company was not good
because at the time of budget the insurance sector was
greatly affected because the
insurance sector was earlier in the avatars of tax saving  It used to be available
but after 62,
investment in the insurance sector was not mandatory for tax saving
but in this situation any person would want to
shorten his life, if his life will be good then
these works will also be good, so that is why there is a lot of
earthquake in the insurance sector
in the present situation and the
situation of the insurance sector in India is
good and is getting better day by day,
which date can you
write for the insurance sector for the future, in the future the
insurance sector can become one of the growing sectors
and the top most company of the insurance sector
is HDFC Live, now see
HDFC slide, in the present situation it was trading
at four hundred thirty price, it is
down by 7.55 cents in one week and has given a return of four percent in Wandham
and in one year it has given a return of three percent, so
even after such a fall it is running in positive, at the same time
if you
want to invest in an insurance company then you
can share HDFC, the
second company in the insurance sector is
ICICI.  Prudential Life Insurance
Company, which is the second largest company in this division, is
a last resort company. The
reason being its market price is ₹300.
This one, which is down 2-3 percent, has
given a 5 percent return in one month
and is down 23 percent in one year.
In a different situation, ICICI Prudential is
available at a very good valuation and its
PE is lower than ICICI Prudential Life. We
can also date both ICICI Prudential and ICICI Prudential. The
third stock in our list is SBI Life. The listed company in this Diya Relied on a
Government Life Insurance Company is SBI Life. The current
market price of SBI Life is ₹
600. It is
down 3 percent in one month and has
given a 6% return in one year. SBI
live phone number is a leading company in the insurance
sector. This is also a good company
which is
trading at a price of ₹2030. Under verification, its low is  50 has been
running on a very good front for the last week. You
can also add SBI Life Insurance, another leading bank in India.
MI's insurance company is performing very well
except for the home and there is one
company that is
ICICI Lombard. ICICI Lombard is
within the general insurance company. The
current price of ICICI Lombard is
151. Sure, it has happened
in one week. The
mind of fiction is down in one month. The
phone is down in one month. It has given a good return in the year. It is
down a little bit in one week. It has
given 14% return in one month and
4% return in one month. As you can see,
its low is 105. It has recovered a lot after hitting this low on March 50.
This is the only company in the insurance sector which has an obscene number of tips. It is
in the insurance sector and is doing very
well. So you
can also configure the exam but on this four count,
it is one of the leading companies in the insurance sector.
If you also want to invest in these four companies,
you
can invest for the long term, but
before making this investment, you must take
advice from a financial advisor,
this is not a stock recommendation, this is
just a video focused on education, if
you have any stock related
questions, you can ask in the comments below
and the video of our multibagger
is given in the card above, you can see it, if you
like this video then
please like this video, subscribe my
channel and for the future updates, Roasted
Homestay, thank you.